Before I even start, can you just like and make a comment because they're going to attempt to
suppress this video because it's going to be positive and engagement is what will keep it
moving. And while you're at it, consider signing up for my free broadcast channel right here on
IG because we're really trying to get around this metapression. When people would say to me,
Amanda, like stop responding to people who are being mean, et cetera, et cetera, like save your
energy. It used to be really frustrating, namely because they didn't really explain to me what they
meant. They're just kind of like telling me what to do, right? However, with my greater understanding
of energy and the work that I'm doing around energy, I realized that ultimately wherever you
place your energy is where the attention is going to go and your energy can be placed in so many
more valuable places. So knowing that our energy is being mined, here we are on this internet and so
often really good hearted people that really want the truth find themselves entangled in these exchanges
with, well, to be quite honest, bots or paid actors. And as somebody who has absolutely fallen for
that and who will continue to fall for that probably until I like really like master this,
I challenge all of us to really master the art of verbal judo. When someone comes to attempt to
take your energy through insult, figure out how to use their energy and put it back at them.
Consider doing so in the classic phrase of quote unquote killing with kindness.
Except I would challenge us to instead of killing with kindness, which has a really dope alliteration
to it, to hinder with healing. Hinder their attempt at stealing your energy by hurling healing language
at them. Try it in the comments. I know this is an exercise that some might find silly, but I'm really
wanting us to know that what we are going to have to do to get where we want to go is have to change
how we are interacting. And yes, there have been what looks like victories in terms of elections,
et cetera. None of that matters in the long term if we don't change in the deep sense.
So let's try it and let's see how we undermine the negativity that is continuously being mined
here on these apps by meeting it with healing. It's like Aang and Fire Lord Ozai.
You feel me? Cut out the corporate middlemen and purchase my music directly from me.
Head to amandadiva.bandcamp.com and pay whatever price you want for Truth Translator.
This ain't a movement. It's movement music.